<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fedora on hallajs.net</title><link>https://www.hallajs.net/tags/fedora/</link><description>Recent content in fedora on hallajs.net</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.hallajs.net/tags/fedora/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>minikube on Fedora 34 with podman</title><link>https://www.hallajs.net/posts/2021-05-15-minikube-on-fedora-34/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hallajs.net/posts/2021-05-15-minikube-on-fedora-34/</guid><description>A while ago, I had encountered issues while trying to run minikube on Fedora 33 with podman. Strangely enough I did not keep notes on what I did to get it to work and when I did a fresh installation on Fedora 34, the old error haunted me back again.
Leaning from the past mistake, I suppose it&amp;rsquo;s time to start taking notes on what&amp;rsquo;s the error encountered and what did I do to fix it.</description></item><item><title>Fedora Kickstart for Openbox</title><link>https://www.hallajs.net/posts/2020-08-07-fedora-kickstart-for-openbox/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hallajs.net/posts/2020-08-07-fedora-kickstart-for-openbox/</guid><description>For a while now, I&amp;rsquo;ve been installing Fedora either through the netinstall method, or using the server&amp;rsquo;s ISO to install just the base OS before setting up Openbox during the first boot.
However, after the recent OS reinstallation that I had, I wondered if it&amp;rsquo;s actually possible to have an ISO ready for me, with just the change I need and after reading around, I found Kickstart and that&amp;rsquo;s helped me to archieve this goal.</description></item><item><title>Nicer font in Fedora 20</title><link>https://www.hallajs.net/posts/2014-03-22-nicer-font-in-fedora-20/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hallajs.net/posts/2014-03-22-nicer-font-in-fedora-20/</guid><description>Okay, to start this off - I&amp;rsquo;m actually a Crunchbang user. Recently my laptop&amp;rsquo;s hard disk died and while waiting for a replacement, I decided to revive an older laptop of mine and give Fedora a try.
I would say that everything was perfect, well - &amp;ldquo;almost&amp;rdquo; but I simply hated the font! That prompted me to go on a journey to get the font fixed.
Browsing around and I start to notice that I was not the only one with issues.</description></item></channel></rss>